So.How was your day in the Berkshires?
So. 今天过得怎么样 在伯克郡(Berkshires)?
Really nice.
非常棒.
-Did Kevin drive?   -Yep.
-Kevin开的车?   -Yep.
How's he doing?
他开车怎样?
He's getting very comfortable.
他开的非常自在.
-Maybe too comfortable. -How?
-或许太自在了.    -怎么?
He got a speeding ticket.
他得到一张超速罚款单.
In that car?
开他那辆车?
We weren't in a hurry or anything.
我们并不着急或任何事.
He's just very competitive.
他就是特别好强.
If someone passes him,
如果有人超过了他,
he has to drive faster.
他就要开的更快.
I don't like it at all.
我不喜欢那样 一点也不.
Just before he got the ticket,
就在他得到罚款单前,
a Porsche went by.
一辆保时捷超过了他.
He tried to keep up with a Porsche?
他试图追上保时捷?
That's very sad.
那真令人难过.
Really.But that's not the worst.
Really. 但那不是最糟糕的.
He refuses to ask for directions.
他拒绝问路.
So does Dean! I hate that.
Dean也是这样! 我恨那个.
We were wandering around western Massachusetts,
我们兜圈子 在Massachusetts西部,
and he didn't have a clue about where we were.
并且他毫无头绪我们在哪儿.
But would he stop at a gas station and ask?
可是他会停下来在加油站问问吗?
No!
不!
They have to discover it for themselves.
他们必须自己发现它.
And then,an hour later,
然后, 一个小时以后,
when they accidentally stumble upon the place,
当他们碰巧发现了地方,
they say, "See?I told you.
他们说, "看见没?我告诉你了"
I knew where it was."
"我知道它在哪儿."
-男人啊!  -男人啊!